Re-Sync & Improved By: FidelPerez
Subtitle By: explosiveskull
Sub Upload Date: August 23, 2018
(WIND RUMBLING)
(BOAT CREAKING)
(COUGHS)
(CREAKING CONTINUES)
Richard? Richard?
(GRUNTING)
Hey! Richard!
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
Richard!
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
Rich!
(GRUNTING)
Richard!
(GASPING)
(YELPS)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
Please, no. Please, no.
Please, no.
Please, no. Please.
(GASPING HEAVILY)
No!
(SOBBING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- TAMI: Bye.
- Thank you. Bye, Tami.
(CHUCKLING) Bye.
- Bye, guys.
- MAN: Bye.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Bonjour.
What is your profession?
Uh, whatever job
pays me enough
to get me to the next place.
How long will you be here
in, uh, Tahiti?
No idea.
And your final destination?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- Okay.
- (STAMP THUDS)
(TAMI SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DEB: Hey. So why Tahiti?
What brought you here?
TAMI: The wind, I guess.
I was a cook on a schooner.
But when the gig was up,
I didn't really feel like
going home yet.
DEB: Uh-huh.
Where is home for you?
San Diego. California.
Nice.
When are you going back?
Never. (CHUCKLES)
I don't know. Maybe once
I've seen the world.
Hey, mate.
Why's your boat
called Mayaluga?
It's Swazi.
I'm a Kiwi.
I need a translation, please?
"One who crosses the horizon."
Oh.
You, uh... You girls want
to give me a hand?
Wow, this is so beautiful.
Thanks. Here.
Sorry, what was your name?
- Richard.
- Richard, I'm Deb.
Hi, Deb.
This is Tami.
Hey.
Tami.
Thank you.
Yeah, no problem.
See you.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
See you around.
(YAWNS)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
TAMI: Hey.
Hey.
I thought you may need this.
How thoughtful.
- Thanks, Tami.
- No worries.
Do you, uh,
like fish?
I'm actually a vegetarian.
- (LAUGHING) So...
- Right.
I like them
when they're alive.
- (BOTH CHUCKLES)
- I was gonna see
if you just wanted
to grab an early dinner?
Uh...
But seeing as you're...
Do you know what, I can make
a really good
vegetarian version.
That sounds great. (LAUGHS)
- Good, good. Sold.
- Yes. Thank you.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Done.
Do you want me
to grab anything else?
Uh, some vegetables?
(LAUGHING)
I can do that.
TAMI: You've been
to so many places.
So cool.
RICHARD: Yep.
All on this boat?
Uh, just me and her.
Where did you find her?
I actually built her
when I was working in
a boat yard in South Africa.
You built this boat?
RICHARD: Mmm.
That's a big deal.
- That's so impressive.
- (LAUGHS)
It's not.
It is.
Oh, thank you.
Chin, chin.
Cheers.
What's it like sailing
out there all alone?
Uh... Miserable.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Cold.
Utterly awful.
C'mon...
- (CHUCKLES)
- Seriously?
Yeah, seriously.
I mean, you're either,
uh, sunburnt, sleep-deprived,
or seasick,
usually all three at once,
and constantly hungry.
TAMI: Hmm.
Always wet.
And after a few days
there's the hallucinations.
I'm assuming not the fun kind?
Mmm-mmm. I wish.
(CHUCKLES)
If it's not fun,
then why do you do it?
Uh...
It... It's a feeling...
A feeling I can't describe.
Uh, it's intense.
The infinite horizon.
After a few days,
uh, I feel reborn.
You know, just you,
the wind
and the sound of the boat
cutting through the ocean.
(SMACKS LIPS) I'm sorry,
that was incredibly cheesy.
No.
Not at all, actually.
So you must be a sailor too?
TAMI: Mmm...
I love sailing.
But I don't know that I would
consider myself a sailor.
Oh, come on.
- Not like you.
- Yeah, you are.
- I don't believe you.
- (CHUCKLES)
Do you want to take her out?
Right now?
Uh, sure.
(LAUGHS) We could take her out
right now or tomorrow.
- (RICHARD MUMBLES)
- (BOTH LAUGHS)
RICHARD: Whoo-hoo!
- Whoo!
- (WHISTLING)
RICHARD: Yeah!
MAN: Arr!
MAN: You got it, baby!
You got this.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah!
Hey, the sheet's luffing,
should I pull it in?
I didn't think
you were much of a sailor.
I'm not.
I mean, I learned a few things
when I was a cook
on that schooner.
But definitely never crossed
a horizon all alone like you.
- (GRUNTS)
- There we go.
Whoo!
TAMI: Richard!
(SOBBING) Richard!
Richard! Where are you?
(SHUDDERING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Mayday! Mayday!
This is the sailing yacht
Hazana!
(RADIO STATIC)
Does anyone copy? Hello?
Our last recorded position was
a hundred and twenty-nine
degrees west
and latitude twelve north.
- Does anyone copy?
- (RADIO STATIC)
Hello?
(GRUNTING)
(RADIO STATIC)
Mayday!
Is anybody there?
(VOICE BREAKING)
It's my fiancé...
(BOAT THUDDING)
Our boat is sinking.
Mayday!
(GROANS)
(COUGHS)
(VOMITING)
(COUGHING)
(GROANING)
(CRYING)
Where are you?
(CONTINUES CRYING)
(TAMI GRUNTS)
- Where are you taking me?
- (CHUCKLES)
This is unreal. (GIGGLES)
Wow.
Ooh, you're not gonna jump,
are you?
No, of course I'm not.
- Shut up.
- (TAMI LAUGHS)
(♫ SINGING ♫)
♫ Fly me to the... ♫
RICHARD: Don't! Tami, no!
Tami?
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(SHOUTS)
Tami?
Tami, are you okay?
(TAMI GRUNTS)
(BOTH GASPS)
- (BOTH WHOOP, LAUGHING)
- (RICHARD SHOUTING)
(RICHARD WHOOPS)
(TAMI LAUGHING)
Where'd you become so wild?
What? What does that
even mean? (LAUGHS)
I've never met anyone
like you.
Fearless, like a bloke.
- TAMI: Like a bloke? (LAUGHS)
- (RICHARD GRUNTS)
I guess I've never met
anyone like you either.
Oh, yeah?
Sensitive like a woman.
(GIGGLES)
(TAMI SCREAMS)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
(LAUGHS)
(FAINT THUDDING)
(BOAT CONTINUES THUDDING)
The dinghy.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, my God!
Rich, you're...
(MOTOR SPUTTERING)
Come on, you. Come on.
Ugh! Dammit!
- (GRUNTING)
- (METAL CREAKS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (METAL CREAKING)
- (METALLIC WHIRRING)
- No, no. No!
(MUFFLED WHIMPERING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(GASPS) It's drifting.
It's drifting!
(GASPING AND GRUNTING)
Stop!
(GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(COUGHING)
I'm coming!
I'm just going to make
some repairs.
All right. Here we go, girl.
Let's get you moving.
Looking good, mama.
- (CRACKLES)
- Aah!
(GROANS)
Hell yeah.
(PANTING) What are you?
Got the jib.
Let's get this water
out of here.
Yeah... (PANTING)
We can do this.
Stay.
No, no, no, no, no.
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
- (METALLIC RATTLING)
- (TAMI GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Stay.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
(GRUNTS)
Work with me, girl.
Looking good.
(GRUNTS)
All right, baby,
show me what you got.
Come on!
(CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
- Coming, baby!
- (METAL CREAKING)
(GRUNTS)
- (BOAT RUMBLES)
- (LAUGHS)
- TAMI: What is that?
- (RICHARD LAUGHS)
(TAMI CHUCKLES)
For me?
For you.
It's not my birthday,
you know?
- I know. I... (LAUGHS)
- (TAMI GIGGLES)
I saw it in a window
and I thought of you. Uh...
(TAMI GIGGLES)
You don't like it?
No, I love it. I...
It's beautiful.
(BOAT RUMBLING AND CREAKING)
(GRUNTS)
TAMI: Okay.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Richard!
Almost there.
(METAL CREAKING)
Hang on!
Oh, my God, you're alive!
Oh, my God! (CRIES)
(PANTING)
- (RICHARD GROANING WEAKLY)
- (TAMI GRUNTING)
(RICHARD BREATHING LABORIOUSLY)
(TAMI GRUNTING AND PANTING)
(TAMI GRUNTS)
(TAMI GRUNTING)
(RICHARD GROANING)
(RICHARD COUGHS)
- (TAMI GRUNTS)
- (WATER SPLASHES)
(RICHARD COUGHING)
TAMI: Oh, my God.
- (SOFTLY) Hi. Hi.
- (RICHARD SHIVERING)
Hi, I'm here. I'm here.
Look at me.
It's gonna be okay.
(RICHARD CONTINUES SHIVERING)
(PANTING) It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay. Okay.
(RICHARD GASPS)
(CRIES)
Okay, tell me, do you, uh...
Do you know what flower
that is?
It's a plumeria, right?
It's a frangipani.
- A what?
- A frangipani.
- It's a... Yeah.
One second. Here you go.
TAMI: That's what you call it?
The flower of love.
It's like God
put these on Earth
to mask the smell
of burning trash.
(BOTH LAUGHS)
My late mum used to say
that nothing
moves through life faster.
In one day, one can open,
it can change color,
wilt, and then die.
Look...
Here, pass it, pass it.
Sometimes
the things that you say...
Left or right?
Uh... Uh, why?
It's very, very important.
- (CAR HORN HONKING)
- You choose.
Basically,
if you choose your left,
it means you are technically
off the market,
you're in a relationship.
- Ooh.
- Yeah, so it's...
Well...
Wow, wise choice. Wise choice.
(♫ SOFT OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
- TAMI: Seven years?
- Mmm-hmm.
Wow.
So that would mean
that when you were
beginning to work
on the Mayaluga,
I was celebrating my sweet 16?
- (LAUGHS)
- Yep.
Jeez.
And was it sweet, your 16th?
No. No, my mom
took me to my first bar.
I had like 10 shots
of Midori...
Oh, my Lord.
Yeah. Worst hangover
of my life, hands down.
So your mum's a wild one, eh?
One of those
young-at-heart types?
Oh, she's just young, period.
She was 31.
Oh, when she had you?
No. No, that night.
She was 15 when she had me.
Wow.
Got knocked up
when she was just a kid.
Had me out of defiance.
My dad's parents
actually raised me.
What was that like?
It was what I knew.
I don't know.
I made attempts, of course,
to run away.
But Mom worked for TWA,
and I think her
not being around as much
kind of forced me
to stick around.
Like I owed it to her
to finish high school
or something.
- That makes sense.
- I guess.
But, man,
the day I graduated, I split.
My girlfriend and I
had been saving up,
and we bought the sickest bus,
drove it across the border
to Todos Santos
and just lived on the beach
for a few months.
We started a salsa company
and surfed every day.
It was...
(EXHALES) It was amazing.
Plan was to stay
for six months,
but it's been five years
and here I am...
Here you are.
(LAUGHS)
You ready to shake, old salt?
(LAUGHS) Sorry...
- Can I say no? No. No, no.
- Yes. Yes.
(BOTH LAUGHS)
(♫ POLYNESIAN MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
- Oh, you have been warned.
- (BOTH LAUGHS)
I'm sorry this...
This is the best I've got.
No, you've got more in there,
I know it. (LAUGHS)
Oh, no. No,
you're a much better dancer.
TAMI: It's the dress.
It is the dress.
That's why you bought it
for me.
Ah, got me.
(MUSIC ENDS)
(♫ SOFT POLYNESIAN MUSIC
PLAYING ♫)
Hey, Tami...
Yeah?
Will you sail around the world
with me?
(TAMI CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(RICHARD WINCING, GROANING)
TAMI: Exhale for me.
(RICHARD BREATHING SHARPLY)
(GROANS)
(TAMI SHUSHES)
- Hey, it's okay. It's done.
- (GROANS)
Just breathe.
(GROANING LOUDLY)
What? What, what, what, what?
My ribs. My ribs. My ribs.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
(RICHARD PANTING)
TAMI: Put your arm around me.
- Ready? One, two, three, lift.
- (RICHARD GROANS)
- Okay, okay...
- (RICHARD COUGHS)
(TAMI SHUSHING)
- (COUGHS, GROANS)
- Shh.
(RICHARD CHUCKLES)
What about Fatu Hiva?
We could sail there first.
It could work.
It could work, yeah.
As long as we don't
go through Hana Vave.
Everyone goes through it,
it's become a bit of a dump.
Oh, what's the draw then?
Better anchorage.
Lazy suckers.
Omoa Bay. Now that...
That is, I mean,
that is parfait.
Yeah? What, the beaches?
Yeah.
Just like beyond amazing.
(BOTH SPEAK FRENCH)
(IN ENGLISH) What about Japan?
I've always wanted
to check it out.
- Are you kidding me?
- Mmm-mmm.
It's like
my number one place, like...
- Really?
- Yeah.
We gotta go.
How long do you think
it would take to sail there?
- Forever. But does it matter?
- No.
No. God, I just want to go
everywhere with you.
Then everywhere we will go.
WOMAN: Richard! Richard!
MAN: Richard!
- (MAN LAUGHS)
- What? Tally-ho!
MAN: Where the hell
have you been hiding?
How are you, mate? (LAUGHS)
Oh, just everywhere.
WOMAN: Good to see you,
Richard.
I nearly rang the bloody
coast guard. (LAUGHS)
Sorry. Sorry, this is...
This is Tami. Tami.
- Hi.
- Christine.
- Christine. Peter.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi, my pleasure.
- Same.
Tami. Yeah, well...
How have you guys been?
- Oh, really good.
- Great.
We were just off for a coffee,
do you want to join us?
PETER: I'm glad we bumped
into you, Richard, because...
Well, there's something
we'd like
to talk to you about,
actually.
CHRISTINE:
The thing is, Richard,
we've got to go back to London
rather suddenly,
and we wanted to ask
if you'd be interested in...
Yeah, we've been trying
to find someone,
and I don't know
if you'd be keen, but...
How'd you like
to sail the Hazana
back to California for us?
We can pay $10,000
plus a first-class ticket
return.
Seriously?
You're...
You're joking, right?
- No, mate.
- No.
PETER: What do you say?
(LAUGHS) Uh...
(LAUGHS) Where...
Where in California?
- PETER: San Diego.
- (TAMI CHUCKLES)
Wow. (CHUCKLES)
Uh... I don't mean
to look a gift horse
in the mouth here,
but is there any possibility
of making it two tickets back?
Done and done.
Done and done. Brilliant!
Wow. That is... (LAUGHS)
When do you leave?
Well, we're hoping to get out
no later than next week.
And the things is,
we don't want to press you,
but it would be great
if you could
let us know
when you could set sail.
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, we can do that.
- CHRISTINE: Great.
- We can, um,
- mull it over. (LAUGHS)
- (CHRISTINE LAUGHS)
Are you sure
you want to put me in charge
of these numbers?
I'm shit at math.
You can do anything
you put your mind to.
Mom used to tell me
the same thing.
And then she would say that
my mind was too strong.
Probably should have just been
more like her, huh?
Have kids by now.
Live in the suburbs somewhere.
Well, I'd still be
in the Naval Academy
if I'd listened to me dad.
But I decided to live
my own life.
(SIGHS)
(METAL CREAKING)
We're...
We're so far north!
Well, we are drifting.
How far?
Way further than I thought.
What's the latitude?
Eighteen degrees north.
That's like a fifteen hundred
square mile search area...
- (TAMI SIGHS)
- (GROANS)
We're gonna die out here.
We're not on any flight paths,
there's no shipping lanes...
Tami...
No one knows we're here.
We'll be fine.
(SNIFFLES)
(EXHALES)
Hey.
You okay?
I don't want to feel like
I'm following you
on your adventures.
I get that it's
a really cool opportunity,
but I'm not really looking
to go home yet.
It's not the direction
I wanna go in,
and if that's what
you want, then...
I'm sorry.
I'm not going.
I'm not asking you to do that.
I know.
I sailed half the world
to find you.
I'm not just letting that go.
(CHUCKLING) What?
Ugh. (CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
Well, can I see
this big bad boat?
- The boat's fifty-five feet...
- (BEEPS)
(GRUNTING) Fourteen seconds...
Means we're going about
two... two-and-a-half knots.
We could hit San Diego
in twenty-five days.
But then with these headwinds,
it could take months...
Well, what if we don't sail
to San Diego?
What do you mean?
TAMI: I mean,
what if we hang left
and we go to Hawaii?
Like navigators did
back in the day.
Yeah, but most of those
sailors didn't make it, Tam.
If you miss Hawaii...
I know,
there's nothing till Japan.
It's like a two thousand mile
shot at a moving target.
If we miss Hawaii, we die.
We'd be adding
five hundred miles.
Yeah, but the current and
the wind would be behind us.
(TAMI SIGHS)
RICHARD: Okay.
Take a left
on the nineteenth...
TAMI: Yeah.
(CREAKING)
CHRISTINE: The moment we hit
the dock, I cried out,
"God, I'm glad to be back
in Rangiroa!"
PETER:
There's a fellow nearby,
he looks to his wife
and he says to us,
"You're not in Rangiroa...
- "You're in Apataki."
- No.
How? That's like 100
miles away!
- Yeah, no shit.
- (ALL CHUCKLES)
The longest sail of my life,
Richard.
- Sorry about that, darling.
- (LAUGHTER)
Well, cheers, everyone.
ALL: Cheers.
What's the, uh... What's
the rush back to London,
- if you don't mind me asking?
- Ah.
Well, it's Christine's father,
he's not well.
- TAMI: Oh.
- RICHARD: I'm sorry.
Will he be okay?
He's ninety-four.
It's a good innings.
You'd be a life-saver,
Richard.
Wow.
This is beautiful. (CHUCKLES)
Oh, Richard.
We're out of ginger beer...
We're just gonna go and grab
some from the clubhouse. Okay?
Make yourselves at home.
We'll be back in a while.
Thanks.
(TAMI SNICKERING)
So, what do you think of
the big bad boat then?
I think four thousand miles
is insane...
Yeah, but
in a month
we'd make enough to fund
an entire year
traveling together.
- Oh, a year?
- Ah.
Who said anything
about a year?
(EXHALES) Why are you
trying to get rid of me?
Why are you
trying to have sex with me?
Why not? Here?
I mean, it's our boat now,
so why not?
(EXCLAIMS)
So you're in?
Just for those first-class
plane tickets.
Whoa.
- Later, you dirty old man.
- Come on.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
TAMI: Dear Mum,
sorry it's been a while.
I wanted to let you know that
I am going to be coming home.
I got this job sailing
this gorgeous yacht
from down here
back to San Diego.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
It's about
a thirty-day crossing,
so hopefully we'll get there
right before Halloween.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- (WHIRRING)
(GASPS) It looks like we have
a quarter tank of water!
I really hope you're in town
because I'm going
to be bringing
my new boyfriend. (CHUCKLES)
His name is Richard.
He's a little bit older.
Uh, he's from England.
We've only been together
a few months now,
but, I don't know, I really
feel like he's the one.
DEB: Bon voyage, lovers.
TAMI: I guess we'll find out
after crossing the Pacific
together. (CHUCKLES)
Anyway,
I can't wait to see you
and Gram and Grandpa.
Dad, if he's around.
I'll see you soon.
I love you so much.
(GROANS) That's it.
We've eaten
all the fresh stuff.
Ouch. (EXHALES)
Is this it?
Yeah. It's everything
I could salvage.
- Here. You need to drink this.
- (EXHALES)
Come on.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SLURPS)
Okay, close your eyes.
Are you ready
to love me even more?
Look. Open your eyes.
Is that peanut butter?
Ha. (CHUCKLES)
(SNIFFS)
(SIGHS)
RICHARD: Do you want a hand?
No. I got it.
(TAMI GRUNTS)
(RICHARD GROANS)
Oh.
How much do you
love me right now?
- (RICHARD MOANS)
- Huh?
- Is it good?
- RICHARD: Mmm.
(MUFFLED) It's so good.
(MOANS)
Oh, my God.
RICHARD: Wow.
So what do you think of that?
- Huh?
- TAMI: It's so red.
- RICHARD: Come on.
- What?
What, is that
how you'd describe
a painting by Monet? Red?
- If it was red, I would.
- Red.
- Yeah.
- (BOTH CHUCKLES)
RICHARD: No. No.
That sunset's not red.
That sunset
is beet-dyed pomegranate.
(BOTH LAUGHS)
Ladies and gentlemen,
Bob Ross. (LAUGHS)
Can you see... I say
it's kind of got a beety...
It's definitely red.
RICHARD: No, no, no.
With a hit
of mandarin and flax
and the faintest hint
of carnelian.
Red. (CHUCKLES)
Red sky at night.
Sailor's delight.
Who the hell is Bob Ross,
anyway?
You don't know
who Bob Ross is?
Should I?
He's like
the master of kitsch.
Uh, he's like
a modern-day Monet.
You would love him. (CHUCKLES)
- (CHUCKLES)
- Wait a second...
- Aw.
- (RICHARD LAUGHING)
- Wait, let me see you. Wait...
- (BOTH LAUGHS)
Your cheeks,
they're going to...
RICHARD: Let me guess,
they're red?
No, no.
It's definitely not red.
More like, um,
a sizzling salmon ketchup.
(BOTH LAUGHS)
(BOAT CREAKING)
RICHARD: Tam?
What is it?
TAMI: Hold on.
We're off sixty miles.
And we lost a degree
of latitude.
We... How?
TAMI: I don't know!
Maybe the clock's not working?
(GRUNTS) Or I messed up
the math or something?
We're over eighteen hundred
miles from Hawaii.
Fricking rudder's not helping.
(EXHALES) It's making it
impossible to stay on course.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oi, no, no, no.
We need to ration now.
Okay, you wanna
starve to death?
You wanna be a victim,
be my guest.
You make it sound like
it's a choice.
- It is a choice, Tam.
- It's not a choice!
- (METAL CREAKING)
- (TAMI SIGHS)
- (CREAKING CONTINUES)
- Shut up!
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WINCING AND PANTING)
You okay?
(WINCING)
(GROANS)
(TAMI PANTS)
(GRUNTING)
TAMI: It has a jib
caught on it.
I can't get it off.
Maybe it'll have
to just trail.
And create all that drag?
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(SNIFFS)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(RICHARD WINCING)
- Babe?
- How is it?
It's okay.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(RICHARD WINCING)
(RICHARD BREATHING SHARPLY)
(GRUNTING)
RICHARD: Is everything okay
down there?
Yeah.
We're running low on water.
Seven cans of sardines.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Nine cans...
of God knows what.
Let's pray for peaches.
Fortunately, I think
it's gonna be beans.
Three cans of Spam.
Ugh.
Thank God,
the bloody hot sauce
didn't break though.
This isn't gonna
last us a week.
Well...
We can supplement
with protein.
TAMI: I'm not doing that.
- I'm not gonna kill any fish.
- Why not?
'Cause I'm not gonna
make something suffer.
That food's not gonna
last us till Hawaii.
I know it's not.
Sorry.
My ribs are broken,
my leg is shattered.
I'm dead weight.
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
RICHARD: Just relax.
Easy for you to say.
All right, well, remember
it could be worse.
Could die of hunger.
(GRUNTS FRUSTRATEDLY)
(INHALES)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS) I can't do it.
It's too hard.
(TAMI GRUNTING)
RICHARD: It's okay.
I can't do it. (GASPING)
(SHUSHING)
(LAUGHING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(LAUGHS)
TAMI: What you got
hiding in here?
What?
(CHUCKLES)
No way. We've struck gold.
Are you kidding me right now?
We're gonna have a party!
(LAUGHS)
A little touch of humanity...
(♫ SLOW GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
(♫ SINGING ♫) ♫ Well, I turn around
to look at you ♫
♫ Light a cigarette ♫
♫ I wish I had the guts
to bum one ♫
♫ You don't know me yet ♫
♫ And I hope that
I don't fall in love with you ♫
♫ 'Cause falling in love
just makes me blue ♫
♫ Well, the music plays ♫
♫ And you display your heart
for me to see ♫
I wish you'd never met me...
So you wouldn't be
in this mess.
But I wouldn't have us
to remember.
I wouldn't trade this
for anything.
(♫ SOFT GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING ♫)
(♫ SINGING ♫)
♫ 'Cause falling in love ♫
♫ Just makes me blue ♫
♫ I had a beer and now I hear ♫
♫ You calling out for me ♫
♫ Well, I think that I just ♫
♫ Fell in love with you ♫
(LAUGHS)
Come on.
Hey, babe,
can I ask you something?
Sure.
How did your mum die?
Uh, you really want to know?
You don't have to tell me.
Just... Curious.
When I was seven,
she hung herself.
What?
Yeah, it... It's fine.
It's...
It's years ago now. So...
Wow, I'm so sorry.
But, Christ,
the first person in your life
who dies is supposed
to be old, you know?
Not your bloody mother.
Uh, I think what I've done
over the years
is just sort of...
Sort of internalized.
What? Internalized what?
Her voice, I guess.
Yeah.
Like, in my mind, I still...
I still ask her
to take a look at things.
And still listen to her
tell me
if something is right
or wrong, or...
What is she saying now?
(LAUGHS)
Uh...
(CHUCKLES)
"So it's true
what they say, innit?
"All men really do
wanna marry their mums."
(RICHARD LAUGHS)
Oh, fuck, did I just ask you
to marry me
in the voice
of my dead mother?
Oh, God.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, let me...
Let me try that one more time.
I love you.
TAMI: Mmm-hmm...
And I know that
I wanna be with you forever.
So, uh...
Oh, my God.
Will you please marry me?
You're not supposed
to say "please."
You make it sound like
it's a favor. (LAUGHS)
Right. Uh... Okay.
But yes, yes.
- Should I...
- Of course.
Sorry. I must have made it
too small.
- Is that... Is that all right?
- Did you make this?
Yes, well...
But I promise when we get back
to the States,
we can get you a real one.
No.
It's perfect.
(RUMBLING)
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Hey!
Hello!
I'm right here!
Stop! Hello!
No. No...
No! No!
(WHIMPERING)
No, no, no...
How could you not see us?
We're right here!
Where did you go?
(PANTING)
I'm hallucinating?
Am I hallucinating? (SOBS)
Oh, my God,
we're gonna die out here!
We're gonna die out here!
RICHARD: We might.
You're not supposed
to say that!
You'd rather I lied to you?
Yes, please lie to me.
Just tell me
it's gonna be okay.
Tell me that this is real.
RICHARD:
What does that even mean?
(RICHARD GROANS)
(TAMI GROANS)
We're probably dead already.
RICHARD: Exhausted...
Dehydrated...
Delirious, uh...
Yeah. But you're not dead.
(SOBS QUIETLY)
(SNIFFS, GROANS SOFTLY)
Okay. Wake up.
Baby, you've got to drink
some water. Open.
- More. One more.
- Uh-uh.
Come on.
You have to eat something too.
It's more important
you have it.
TAMI: There's plenty for me.
Open.
Dammit, take a bite.
You have to eat something.
You let me sleep
through the night again?
Yeah.
And another night.
And another day.
Just wake me up
when we get to Hawaii.
Guess what?
We only have 690 miles to go.
- (TAMI CHUCKLES)
- Only?
Yeah, only, baby.
No, no. Stay awake.
Look at me.
Look... Look, look, look...
I'm the...
I'm the one
who crosses the horizon.
I'm a real sailor!
(WIND WHISTLING)
Whoa!
What was that?
Babe, you've got to come
see this!
Is that a land bird?
Yeah.
What's it doing
this far from shore?
I don't know. The wind
must have blown her in.
All the way from land?
I think so.
It's remarkable, right?
Should we be worried?
Hey, take the wheel,
I've just got to check this.
(RADIO BEEPS)
MAN: (ON RADIO) A warning
to those in the Pacific.
High winds
and expected rainfall
are now changed to
a tropical depression
forming off Central America,
and is now
classified as a Class 4.
It's moving quickly
and increasing in strength,
currently at 12 degrees north
and 107 degrees
and moving west at 12 knots.
Babe, that's not good...
And a repeat, for those of you
just tuning in.
- Babe?
- Just one sec, please.
Right, so we're at 11 north
and 123 west.
That's well over
1,000 miles away
from the center of the storm.
It should die out
before it reaches us, but...
We have to watch this one.
What if we just alter
our course?
RICHARD: Huh?
We cut north,
give the storm a wider berth.
What do you think of that?
RICHARD:
You're right, let's do it.
We need to make sure
everything is secure.
Yeah, we need to tack first.
All right, let's tack.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- All right, lock it up.
- Yep.
We don't want
any stuff flying around
in case the storm hits.
TAMI: Hey, I'll get that.
TAMI: Look at that. Wake up.
What do you make of that?
It's pink absinthe.
RICHARD: Hmm.
And bloody marigolds
in Hawaiian reduction.
It's red.
- Did you just say "red"?
- (WEAKLY) Mmm.
You coming round to my side?
Tami, it's red.
It is. Finally. (CHUCKLES)
It's red. It's red...
Red sky in the morning...
Sailors take warning...
Another fricking storm?
(GRUNTING)
Hey, babe.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Christ, you're burning up.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna build a shelter
for the storm.
Okay? Okay.
(GRUNTS)
Let the sheet go!
What?
Let the sheet off now!
Okay.
(TAMI PANTING)
(RICHARD GRUNTING)
Help! Take the halyard off!
(TAMI SCREAMS)
It's released!
RICHARD: Help me!
(TAMI WHIMPERING)
TAMI: It was just a squall.
It's amazing, isn't it?
How just a little sheet
can make
the whole world
feel like it disappears?
- Do you see?
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
When I was little,
my dad used to come visit
at my grandparents' house.
We never knew
when he was coming,
he would just show up.
When he arrived,
I would get so excited
because he was
my favorite person
in the whole world.
He would take me surfing
and get me ice cream and...
The next morning,
he would always be gone.
We never knew
where he was going,
he would just disappear.
And then starting
when I was about ten,
my grandparents
stopped letting him in
when he would show up.
And he would just fly
into a rage.
Screaming and shouting and...
I heard a lot of things
that most young girls
never have to hear.
(FLAGS FLAPPING)
But when it was happening,
I would go into the bathroom,
I would lock the door
and get in the bathtub,
and I'd put a blanket
over the shower rod,
and I'd pretend like
I was anywhere else
in the whole world.
(WIND RUMBLING)
We could do that right now.
We could pretend
we were somewhere else.
MAN: (ON RADIO)
Hurricane Raymond
is now classified
as a Category 4...
Mayday! Mayday!
This is the sailing yacht
Hazana. Do you copy?
We need to head southwest!
Are you sure?
If we can't get above it,
maybe we can sneak below it!
What did you say?
Nothing. Just...
Just get the EPIRBs.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(TAMI YELPING)
- (RICHARD GROANS)
- (TAMI PANTING)
I love you.
RICHARD:
Do you want me to go?
TAMI: I got it!
RICHARD: Be careful!
(TAMI GRUNTING)
RICHARD: Hold on! Hold on!
- I've got you!
- (SCREAMS) Richard! Richard!
RICHARD: It's all right!
It's all right.
(TAMI WHIMPERING)
Are you okay?
TAMI: Yeah. Yeah.
RICHARD: I thought I'd
lost you there for a minute.
TAMI: You're not gonna
lose me.
RICHARD: Now, get below.
It's safer.
I'm not going down
without you!
We could roll!
The boat will right itself.
Get below!
I'm not leaving you!
Get below now!
TAMI: Oh, my God!
RICHARD: Tam, get in now!
You need to get in. Go!
TAMI: Here... Here...
Put your safety harness on!
(RICHARD SCREAMS)
(TAMI SCREAMS)
(TAMI GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(SOFTLY) Tam...
Tami...
Get up.
Now.
Richard...
I'm gonna let you go now.
(SIGHS)
I'll love you forever.
(METAL RATTLES)
(TAMI GROANING WEAKLY)
RICHARD: And after a few days,
there's the hallucinations.
Are you ready to love me
even more?
(MOANS)
TAMI: If I hadn't met you,
then I wouldn't have us
to remember.
I wouldn't trade this
for anything.
(SNIFFLES)
(CRIES)
I have to do this
on my own now.
(GRUNTS)
(SPUTTERING)
(BIRD WARBLING)
Hi.
You're back.
What are you doing here?
Where did you come from?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(SIGHING)
(SHIP HORN BELLOWS)
(GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMING)
- (SHIP HORN BELLOWS)
- (LAUGHS)
- (PANTING)
- (SHIP HORN BELLOWS)
CREWMAN: Are you okay?
Okay, we got you.
Yeah. Can you tie up
the stern line?
(SNIFFS)
Mmm.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SNIFFLES)
(LAUGHS)